ALEB HOULDIN

Shieldfield, Newcastle, NE2 1BU | calebhoulding@gmail.com | 07916 037020

summary

- Diligent
- Strong Listener
- Friendly & Easy to Work With
- Efficient & Fast Learner
- Positive Attitude
- Confidence in Forward-Facing Roles
- Valuable Social Skills
- Experience in Fast-Paced Work Environments
- Cellar Trained

interests German Language

Foreign Countries & Cultures 3D Graphics & Graphic Design Cooking **Art & Photography Computers & Electronics**

digital proficiency

Experience Linux (Debian & Arch based distributions); Windows (7-10) Command Prompt; Windows Server; Active Directory; C#; Python; HTML; CSS; Microsoft Office; Adobe Photoshop; Adobe Illustrator; Adobe Lightroom

Exposure JavaScript; PHP; SQL; Blender; Adobe InDesign; Adobe Premiere Pro; Adobe After Effects

work experience

Bar Team Leader

The Mile Castle, Wetherspoons

September 2021 - January 2022

As a Team Leader at Wetherspoons, responsibilities included managing all of the staff on a bar (delegating jobs, administering breaks, offering help and guidance), dealing with customer issues and customers, ensuring the close gets done reasonably and efficiently, being first in the pub to prep it for open, and sorting out anything that is required within the cellar.

Bar Associate

The Mile Castle, Wetherspoons

May 2021 - September 2021

As a bar associate, responsibilies included serving customers on the bar, delivering drinks and food to tables on the floor, cleaning down the bar on the close, and ensuring service goes smoothly.

IT Technician (Apprentice)

Stickyeyes

September 2019 - September 2020

As part of my position as IT tech, I had to manage infrastructure, offer technical support, manage office electronics, contact suppliers, and complete auditing in a fast paced marketing company. I worked with all teams in the business and frequently worked around the office with all kinds of people. It was both intellectually challenging and physically demanding at times. It was a considerable learning experience and invaluable.

Team Member

Greggs

September 2018 - September 2019

During my time at Greggs, my responsibilities included serving customers, restocking the various products, and preparing all kinds of foods and drinks from breakfast sandwiches to coffees. I improved upon my customer service skills and social abilities.

Team Member

KFC

December 2017 - April 2018

As a team member at KFC, I worked a variety of roles in a fast-paced food environment. My jobs most often included food preparation and working on the tills but were occasionally working on drive thru and working in the middle where I would bag fries, put food into the fryers, prepare burgers and wraps, or box and bag food for drive thru. I also worked on closing shifts which included doing full cleans of the store and getting it perfect for service the next day.

School Work Experience **Dubit Limited**

2016

For my work experience in school, I chose to go to Dubit, a company focused on creating internet and mobile games for children, where I worked as quality assurance. During my time there I learned product improvement, teamwork, and essential communication skills. As part of my time there, I worked on a multitude of mobile applications for younger audiences, testing and using the applications in order to spot their faults and report them to the development team. I also tested more physical gaming experiences such as virtual reality mobile games, testing the user experience rather than functionality. This was an exciting opportunity to help in the development of games utilising new technologies.

education

GCSE

Horsforth School

English Language 6 English Literature 6

Mathematics 6

Religious Studies A
Art and Design (Fine Art) B

Art and Design (Photography) B

Science Core B

Science Additional B Food Technology B

Computer Science B

ECDL level 2 Distinction*

A-LEVEL

Horsforth School

Business Studies C Computer Science C

IT Distinction*

ECDL Level 3 Pass

BA Degree Northumbria University

International Relations & Politics In Progress

experiences

Technology Challenge Premier Farnell

2017

As part of a challenge issued to students from various school, I took part in a technology challenge. The goal was to build a piece of assistive technology, ours being based on arthritis. We were given electronic components including a Raspberry Pi. We designed a pet feeder which got us through to the regional finals. Working closely as a team we developed a functional product - both in the manufacturing side and the technological side. I was project leader of the challenge which led to me learning invaluable leadership skills.

The Challenge

NCS

28th June 2017 - 20th July 2017

A 4-week course consisting of personal challenge, skills, and social action. During the 4 weeks I challenged myself and attempted to conquer fears with persistence during outdoor adventure, gained invaluable skills in public speaking by having to give a talk to my group about a subject of my choice, and aided charities by raising money through sponsors and raising awareness using homemade signs and approaching members of the public on the streets in Leeds.